# POPOV ROMAN

### PYTHON DEVELOPER

+7 (910) 272 37 16

i@romanpopoff.ru

WEBSITE.com

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a Python developer with a passion for creating innovative solutions. I have 5 years of experience in the technology industry, which has allowed me to develop a deep understanding of technological systems and successfully implement tasks related to automating production processes. In addition, I am interested in reading scientific articles and traveling.

### **EDUCATION**

DIPLOMA - (2016 - 2018) STATE UNUVERSITY DUBNA, MASTERS DEGREE SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND MANAGEMENT

DIPLOMA - (2012 - 2016)

VOLGOGRAD STATE UNIVERSITY, BACHELOR

LASER TECHIC AND LASER TECHNJLOGIES

### SKILLS

#PYTHON #DJANGO #DRF #FLASK

#PANDAS #ASYNCIO #MULTIPROCESSING

#SQL #REDIS #NODE JS

#JAVASCRIPT #TYPESCRIPT #VUEJS

#NUXT JS #VUEX #BOOTSTRAP

#LINUX #DOCKER

#### EXPERIENCE

### PAO «Tensor» | Dubna | Engineer-Programmer | November 2022 - February 2023

- Designing software in accordance with technological processes;
- Developing software in Python/C++;
- Testing software for compliance with technological requirements;
- · Developing accompanying documentation.

### «Joint Institute for Nuclear Research» | Dubna | Engineer | April 2019 -November 2022

- Designing software in accordance with technological processes;
- Developing software in Python/C++;
- Testing software for compliance with technological requirements;
- Writing technical specifications and developing accompanying documentation.

#### Achievements:

- Developed full-fledged software for controlling coordinate machine mechanisms, which also includes the ability to evaluate material magnetization.
- Developed software for monitoring technical processes, which includes analysis of device status.
- Developed software for monitoring vacuum level in a vacuum chamber.

## «Institute for Physical and Technical Problems» | Dubna | Engineer | February 2018 - November 2018

- · Analysis and evaluation of product manufacturing requirements
- Assembly and configuration of equipment for the nuclear industry **Achievements**:
- Developed software for optimizing components selection for products.

### «Joint Institute for Nuclear Research» | Dubna | Engineer | January 2017 - January 2018

- · Participation in experiments related to research activities;
- Analysis of requirements for experimental parameters;
- Development of programs in C++.

### Achievements:

- Conducted a series of experiments in which I played an important role;
- Developed software for analyzing the effectiveness of scintillation sensors.